I really appreciate it if you're
os agradezco muchísimo eh que estéis
subscribing, if you're giving away
suscribiendo que estéis regalando
subscriptions, really from the heart,
suscripciones de verdad de corazón
thinking that they're going to spend that money
pensar que ese dinero se lo van a gastar
on parties, but it doesn't matter, it's going to be to
en fiestas pero da igual va a ser para
save the turret, we'll be free of
salvarles al tuario nos liberaremos de
that forever, and that's important, very
eso para siempre y eso es importante muy
important, I can't do more, okay. But anyway, I really
importante más no puedo hacer vale Pero
appreciate it from the bottom of my
bueno que os lo agradezco muchísimo y de
heart, and if you see me riding in a
corazón y si me veis montado en un
Mercedes in two months, you know, this
Mercedes dentro dos meses ya sabéis este
animal that I have here is a
animal que tengo aquí es una
little appointment, he's seeing, his
citita está viendo no le va a aguantar
body won't be able to take it, it's going to be very, very difficult for him to
el cuerpo va a ser muy muy difícil que
hold on, he had a
le aguante el cuerpo tenía un problema
serious neurological problem, we're
neurológico gordo fuerte le estamos
giving him a medicine that's strong so
dando una medicina que es fuerte para
that he doesn't have convulsions
que no para que no tenga convulsiones
and obviously that affects his entire
y obviamente eso le afecta a todo su
system, his kidneys are being poisoned,
sistema se está envenenando los riñones
little by little, he's being
están paraliz poco a poco se está
poisoned, so that you understand what's
envenenando para que entendáis lo que
happening once he's
está pasando una vez que se va
poisoned, he's losing his
envenenando Va perdiendo la
life, he's noticing it, he's suffering, no, he's not
vida lo está notando está sufriendo no
suffering at all, in fact, right now he
no está sufriendo nada de hecho ahora
's in a brutal state of relaxation, the
mismo Está con una relajación brutal lo
only thing we can do now is for him to
único que podemos hacer ahora es que se
die
muera
peacefully, he could survive. Well,
tranquila que podría sobrevivir Pues a
maybe he'll survive, I don't know.  but 90 that she's
lo mejor sobrevive no sé pero 90 de que
going to die today that maybe her body
va a morir hoy que a lo mejor el cuerpo
can take it but I don't think so she's half fried she
lo aguanta pero no creo está medio frita
's here now half warm but she doesn't
está aquí ahora medio calentita pero no
even have the strength to open her eyes the
tiene ni fuerza para abrir los ojos la
feeling she's having is that she's
sensación que está teniendo es que se
falling asleep she's not in pain she's not in
está durmiendo no tiene dolor no tiene
any pain she's just
ningún dolor simplemente se encuentra
very tired she's losing strength she's
muy cansada va perdiendo fuerza va
losing steam
perdiendo fuelle
[Music] I
[Música]
think Yuji had the land where
creo que yuji tenía las tierras en las
he had the shrine and he doesn't
que él tenía el santuario y no se las
want to give it back and he wants to rent it out
quiere devolver y se las quiere alquilar
now because they ended the relationship with
ahora porque terminaron la relación con
everything that man did for her I
todo lo que hizo ese hombre por ella
never thought she would do that to me I
nunca pensé que me lo hiciera ella eso
never thought she would do that to me my
nunca pensé que me lo hiciera ella mis
children are wondering and where are the
hijos se están preguntando y dónde está
good people and where are those who
la gente buena y dónde están los que
can help and there is no one there is no
pueden ayudar y es que no hay no hay
answer you have to come we're going to salt we
respuesta tienes que venir vamos a salar
need 4000 subscriptions on the
necesitamos 4000 suscripciones en el
K Channel to be able to save the
Canal de K para poder salvar el
shrine 5 days in a row without stopping to
santuario 5 días seguidos sin parar para
save the shrine on Kik you are seeing
salvar el santuario en kik estáis viendo
the address subscribe or give away
la dirección suscribiros o regalar
subscriptions we are 4 this is it I'm
suscripciones estamos 4 ya está este me
going to leave because it's that we're going to spend it like
voy a ir porque es que lo a pasar como
the other day this guy comes to
el otro día este tío se me viene a la
mind
cabeza el vídeo de
today's video family  How are you I hope you're all feeling
hoy familia Cómo vais Espero que estéis
great Well I'm going to Fran's house
divino Bueno me voy para la casa de Fran
what are we going to do on the live stream now
que vamos a hacer en el directo de ahora
Well let's do they're going to do I mean I'm
Bueno vamos a hacer van a hacer ellos o
telling you eh I'm not very
sea yo ya te digo eh que no estoy muy
knowledgeable in these things no but they're going to make
puesto en estos temas no pero se van a
a paella a paella that is
poner a ser una paella una paella que es
paella and pae a paella that is paella and
paella y pae una paella que es paella y
pae here I'm carrying the bag with two
pae que aquí llevo yo la bolsa con dos
hamburgers to make in the microwave
hamburguesas para hacer el microondas
because well you know that I
porque bueno ustedes sabéis que yo os
love you all very much Not my people from Valencia
quiero mucho No a mi gente de valencia
but the paella that Fran makes he's going to
pero la paella que haga Fran se la va a
eat it Hello hello What's up honey what's up what's up we're
comer Hola hola Qué pasa cariño qué pasa
going to be over there making
qué vamos a estar por ahí haciendo la
paella look there's that [ __ ]
paella mira ahí está el cabronazo ese
look look he's listening to me and he
mira mira que me está escuchando y se y
's getting up I don't know if you can
se está levantando no sé si lo llegáis a
see him He was lying down in his space and he
ver Estaba tumbado en su hueco y me ha
heard me and he's starting to get up But
escuchado y se pone a levantarse Pero tú
why do you want to whisper to me eh man
por qué me quieres surrar eh hombre
mozzarella what what's going on why no no no no no
mozzarela qué qué pasa por qué no no no
no you [ __ ] leave me already [ __ ] you
no no no tú cabrón déjame ya [__] me ti
balls off I'm feeling a little
las pelotas me estoy sintiendo un poco
harassed yeah yes yes yes I'm feeling a
acosado sí sí sí sí esto sintiendo un
little  harassed by this guy man right yes
poco acosado por este tío hombre verdad
yes
a que sí a que sí
eh say if you defend me
eh decir que si ustedes me defendis
well people I said it let's see how it
bueno gente lo he dicho vamos a ver cómo
goes
sale eso
eh there it is there's the paella that I hadn't
eh ahí está ahí está la paella que no me
realized had been
había dado cuenta que sa habían puesto a
cooked and well from here we're going to keep an
cocinarla y bueno desde aquí vamos a
eye on it Hello family How are you we
vigilar un poco Hola familia Qué tal
're live What's up
estáis que estamos en directo Qué pasa
family What's up What's up How are you
familia Qué pasa Qué pasa Cómo estáis
spending the morning of course or I mean we're
echando la la mañana claro o sea
here at noon which would be
nosotros estamos aquí al mediodía que
approximately my
esta sería aproximadamente mi hora de la
Spanish siesta time but of course you're
siesta española pero claro usted estáis
there not 7 in the morning not in the other
ahí no 7 de la mañana no en en el otro
multiverse no Well do you trust this
multiverso no Bueno qué os fiáis mucho
paella too much or what this paella there country
de esta paella o qué esta paella ahí
Oh [ __ ] what's going on I had a
campera Ah [__] qué pasa lo había visto
glimpse of the loris and I thought
de refilón al loris y me creía que se me
an otter had gotten inside me you see the
había metido una nutria adentro veis el
kangaroo Well the kangaroo is currently
canguro Pues el canguro está ahora mismo
in its teens and apart from the fact that it's
en la adolescencia y aparte de que está
rebellious and wants to hit us all the guy
rebelde y quiere pegarnos a todos el tío
goes around all day with his lipstick off do
va todo el día con el pintalabios fuera
you know what lipstick off is not
sabéis lo que es el pintalabio fuera no
this morning in one of these that we
esta mañana en una de estas que que lo
were watching it around here through the camera I
estábamos viendo por aquí por la cámara
wanted  give it back to the sow to the
quería darle tras trás a la cerda a la
boar this is what a tremendous kangaroo eh
jabalí esta o sea tremendo el canguro eh
with how tender it was in February when
con lo tierno que era en febrero cuando
we came eh How bad How bad is
vinimos eh Qué mala Qué mala es la
adolescence how bad is age you don't
adolescencia qué mal es la edad tú no
go growing eh You stay like this
vayas a crecer eh Tú quédate así para
forever
siempre
okay where are we going to the field to the
vale a dónde vamos para el campo para el
field we are not in the field not to the Camp
campo no estamos en el campo no al Camp
to the Camp we go to the field part Ah to the
al Camp vamos a la parte del campo Ah al
camp okay I mean to the other part
campamento vale o sea a la otra parte
of the sanctuary let's go why because we're going to go a
del santuario vamos por qué porque vamos
nice exercise check out some
una un ejercicio lindo revisar una
things we have there with snakes
cositas que tenemos ahí con serpientes
no no aren't you
no
worried so much Eh Eh Eh Eh How can I
no está preocupadísimo Eh Eh Eh Eh Cómo
not worry you're going to kill me I
no me I a preocupar que me vas a matar
have to go back to Seville
que tengo que volver a Sevilla
[Music]
[Música]
conone Jai [
conone Jai
Sit where I sit in there but
Siéntate dónde me siento ahí dentro pero
this has already gone Get inside don't
esto tienes ida ya Métete dentro no
talk nonsense that they don't care come on but
digas burradas que nos valean venga pero
if this is so bad you can't see not like that
si esto está que no ve no así el culo
your ass here don't move Paloma let's start but do
aquí no te muevas Paloma empezamos pero
n't put that in here Fran don't
no vayas a meter eso aquí Fran no vayas
put that in there Fran man don't cut Juan
a poner eso ahí Fran hombre no taja Juan
guarnizo  Ricky Edi no no no no no man no No
guarnizo Ricky Edi no no no no no hombre
man no
no No hombre no
calm down
tranquilidad
calm down let there be no tension in the
tranquilidad que no haya tensión en el
environment take Fran Fran Fran no no no no no
ambiente toma Fran Fran Fran no no no no
nothing's happening but how could
no no pasa nada pero cómo no va a pasar
nothing happen let's see if you die Nothing's happening well nothing's
nada a ver si te muer No pasa nada bueno
happening on Twitter there are worse people
no pasa nada en Twitter hay gente peor
no no no no no no no no no no no but there are already
no no no no no no no no no no no pero ya
many there are but if I
van muchas ya van pero si con que me
had put one in and we would have been more than enough for the
hubiera metido una y íbamos sobrado al
loom more Fran but if with one I would have been
loom má Fran pero si con una me hubiera
more than enough already my god Fran this one is this one is
ido sobrado ya por dios Fran esta está
this one is Telling me things in my
esta está esta está Diciéndome cosas en
ear no no no no no no no no no you did them
el oído no no no no no no no no no las
listening outside joking already eh No
has hecho escuchando fuera coña ya eh No
no kidding there it goes I think it's
no fuera coña ya va ya creo que está
fine eh I think it's done What's it
bien eh creo que ya está que Cómo que
how Paloma Paloma nothing's happening you
cómo Paloma Paloma que no pasa nada tú
trust but but I think that with one it was already
confía pero pero yo creo que ya con una
going Fran Fran but those are two more no
iba Fran Fran pero esos son dos más no
Fran Fran
Fran Fran
Fran all for the sanctuary jav all for the
Fran todo por el santuario jav todo por
sanctuary Well I don't know I do want
el santuario Pues no sé Yo si quiero que
the sanctuary to continue eh Fran I'm
el santuario siga eh Fran las Estoy
listening to them Fran I'm feeling them
escuchando Fran me las estoy sintiendo
in places that I wouldn't like to feel you no
en sitios que no me gustaría sentiras no
Fran no Fran no  Fran Don't do that Fran
Fran no Fran no Fran No hagas eso Fran
Don't do that I really like the
No hagas eso que me gusta mucho la
shirt you've gained a
camiseta has engordado un
little weight moment I have to take a
poco momento que tengo que sacar una
picture for the ch de
foto para la ch de
hoyu And if we start taking it off little by
hoyu Y si empezamos a quitarla poco a
little I
poco muo
judge who hates you enough
juizo quién te odia bastante
ler no who else
ler no quién más
is
est
No man
No hombre
[Music]
[Música]
open Take it off Take it off Take it off because I
hbre Quítamela Quítamela Quítamela que
'm already feeling it too much no
ya la estoy sintiendo demasiado no
Take it off but oh mom but how many
Quítamela pero ay mamá pero cuántos
members have walked for this Fran my
miembros han andado para esto Fran por
God no FR Oh mom No no Oh look look she's
Dios no FR Ay mamá No no Ay mira mira
pissed off No I don't want to I don't want to
está cabreada No no quiero no quiero
look at her on the neck on the neck on the
mirar la en el cuello en el cuello en el
neck Of course on the neck I want to go
cuello Claro en el cuello me quiero ir
dad Oh how nice I want to go I want to
papá Ay qué lindo me quiero ir Me quiero
go I want to go to Seville a little croquette
ir Me quiero ir a Sevilla una croquetita
of Mara guys This isn't bad for
de Mara chavales Esto no es malo para
the snakes let's see what she's going to say she's
las serpientes a ver qué va a decir está
using the snake She's taking it out Yes
usando la serpiente Está sacando Sí
because the snakes live here they have to
porque las serpientes viven aquí hay
catch mice Every week and this
cogerle ratones Todas las semanas y esto
is a job that they've done today
pues es un trabajo que han hecho hoy
to help the sanctuary so that this
para ayudar al santuario para que esto
continues and so that they are here I say it for
siga y para que estén aquí lo digo por
those who say she used the
los que digan ha utilizado las
snakes for this yes and tomorrow  I'm going
serpientes para esto sí y mañana me voy
to take a bath in the water with mozzarella and we'll
a bañar en el agua con mozzarela y
also be using it to try to
también estaremos usándola para intentar
save the sanctuary because here everyone
salvar el santuario porque aquí todos
is paying up. Even Javi. No, no, take the
apoquinar Hasta Javi No no quitarme la
flame away from me please don't touch me don't touch me don't stop it don't do this to
llama porfa no me toques no me toques no
me don't do this to me we'll get into trouble don't do that to me don't do that to me Take it away from me
la liamos no me hagas eso no me hagas
the truth is that you're very
eso Quítamela la verdad es que estás muy
well eh Take it away from me guys today
bien eh Quítamela ya chicos esto hoy
tomorrow are centipedes tomorrow I won't be
mañana son escolopendras mañana no estoy
here tomorrow I'll be in Hong Kong
yo aquí mañana estoy yo ya por Hong Kong
running after people and friends you can
corriendo a la gente y a los amigos se
see them in moments of emergency well
les ve el momentos de emergencia pues
this is an emergency moment
este es un momento de emergencia para
for you to be my friend This is a good moment for you to be my friend eh
bueno para que fueras mi amigo eh de
[ __ ] this
[__] esto
guys I hope you liked it
chavales Espero que os haya gustado
well Oh
bien Ay
poor thing I like the capers more
pobrecito me gustan más las capar
guys Hello hello guys Look at this Ah no do
chicos Hola hola chicos Mirad esto Ah no
n't look at this guys how have you
esto no lo miréis chicos cómo lo habéis
seen Javi I mean Look how many of us are
visto al Javi o sea Mirad Cuántos
here I mean there are five of us here I've
estamos aquí o sea somos cinco aquí yo
never seen so many people in this
nunca he visto tanta gente en este
room no never after the last
cuarto no nunca después de la última
orgy you're not [ __ ] around  that then
[__] no estás tirando palota que luego
an orgy Hey kids an orgy here you didn't
una [__] Oye hios una [__] aquí no lo
know let's go 11 guys and pigeons Come on and
sabías vamos 11 tíos y palomas Hala y
the idiots who aren't watching
los boludos que no están viendo el
live, do you believe them? Well it's not true I
directo que los creen Bueno no es verdad
was also doggy style, we're going to irl
Estaba también perrito nos vamos de irl
guys do you feel like meeting up irl to
chavales os apetece que nos veamos de
dinner we're going to set up four cameras
irl a cenar vamos a poner cuatro cámaras
here so there's stuff crazy night in
aquí para que haya cosas noche loca en
Thailand guys dreaming is beautiful
Tailandia chavales soñar es bonito la
reality 20 something 20 reaching 20 is already
realidad 20 y pico 20 llegar a 20 ya es
the best I mean when we started I said
la [__] o sea yo cuando empezamos dije
if we reach 10 guys it means we reach
si llegamos a 10 tíos es que llegamos a
10 the first day at night that 10 is already
10 el primer día por la noche que ya 10
50,000 bucks it's a lot of money and already
son 50,000 pavos es mucho dinero y ya
reaching 20 is already the best it is to say
llegar a 20 ya es la [__] ya es decir
well it's that I'm buying a sanctuary I'll
bueno es que me compro santuario me
start reading the menu the menu Look let's
pongo yo a leer la carta la carta Mira a
see Give me a chicken serranito eh
ver me Pon un serranito de pollo eh A
See if I can also give me
ver si me puede poner también
sirloin with wiki and a mantecadito Javi
solomillo al wik y un mantecadito Javi
is
está
reading [ __ ] irl irl first eh
leyendo hostias irl irl de primeras eh
guys You're going to see food  Thai
chavales Vais a ver comida tailandesa
here all come the spicy potatoes
aquí todo vengan las papitas bravas
[Music]
[Música]
Heart does break
Heart does
TR learn to be with it If I can't Love
break TR learn to be with it If I can't
Me In pe
Love Me In
won When I
pe won When
May Just doing it Slow Ian turn All of myy
I May Just doing it Slow Ian turn All of
nobody
myy nobody
Why will it
Por qué
be
será
man V Come with me guys this
hombre V Ven conmigo chavales este
Pirulo has been around for a long time do you remember those who
Pirulo desde hace tiempo os acordáis los
know me for a while now had a
que me conocéis ya de tiempo tenía una
leg all messed up let's get fixed up and
pata toda jodida seamos arreglado y
every time we come The guy gets all
siempre que venimos El tío se pone todo
happy all happy
contento todo contento
[Music]
[Música]
what come here come here come here p What
qué ven acá ven acá ven acá p Qué
hair
pasa pelo
[Music]
[Música]
How good Nina let's
Qué buen Nina a
see how good you are this dog we
ver qué buen que eres este perro lo
cure it we deworm it he doesn't have
curamos le desparasitamos que no tiene
one eh he's left clean soft soft
una eh se ha quedado limpio suave suave
soft he's left clean taste look fel we
suave se ha quedado limpio gust mira fel
cure it we clean it a little more and
lo curamos lo limpiamos un má y
out let's see
fuera a ver vamos
Ace he has to clean the dishes
Ace que tiene que limpiar los platos
10 eur no 9 Not bad It's four
10 eur no 9 No está mal Son cuatro
cokes one of water four plates 9
coca-colas una de agua cuatro platos 9
Not bad Javi has eaten one of  two
No está mal Javi ha comido una de dos
balls two little balls Javi ate
pelotas dos pelotillas ha comido Javi
guys we're done irl we're done Yeah because we're
chavales acabamos irl acabamos Sí porque
already going home and like that wow what a bomb
ya vamos para casa y así buah vaya bomba
guys what's going to happen
chavales lo que va a pasar
now I'm going to sleep and I'm going to look at the
ahora me voy a dormir y voy a mirar a la
bed before going to bed well that it's not
cama antes de acostarme bien que no esté
drunk What are you doing Javi trying to
bomo Qué estás haciendo Javi intentando
open the door again can he get out or
abrir la puerta otra vez puede salir o
can't you open it for this one for
no le podéis abrir a este por
[Laughter]
[Risas]
please what are you doing with my shirt
favor qué haces tú con mi camiseta
because it's catching my current you're
porque me está agarando corriente estás
balls out let's see Javi It's
pendo los huevos vamos a ver Javi Es que
the second time Come on wait damn you
la segunda vez Dale espera [__] lo
press it and give it to one side
presionas y le das para un lado
maybe Hit the gossip you have to
puede ser Dale al chisme lo tienes que
move it to one
mover para un
side to the
lado para la
right
derecha
[Music]
[Música]
damn nobody comes in here you [ __ ] in a
[__] aquí no entra nadie ya cagis en un
bin we all don't even have a doorknob
cubo todos no tenemos ni para pomo
we want 400 subscribers we don't even have
queremos 400 suscriptores no tenemos ni
doorknobs the you what have you locked yourself
pomos la puerta los te qué has encerrado
in a bathroom tell us come out the animals
en un baño cuéntanos sal los animales
of the sanctuary Well look there's a guy right now
del santuario Pues mira hay un ch ahora
with the anes sanctuary incredible
mismo con los anes santuario increíble
the kangaroo is in his teens and
el canguro está en plena adolescencia y
wants to [ __ ] literally
se quiere [__] literalmente a
anyone eh he's a bit of a [ __ ]  kangaroo I
cualquiera eh es un poco [__] el canguro
've literally seen it three or
literalmente lo he visto ya tres o
four times trying to hit
cuatro veces intentar darle por detrás a
the sow from behind I mean gbel I thought you
la cerda me refiero a gbel Yo pensaba
were all from Thailand Yes I have
que todos erais de Tailandia Sí yo tengo
the seat from there in
el asento de ahí de
suratan guys we have to say Goodnight
suratan chicos hay que decirle Buenas
to Javi who is leaving us he has to
noches a Javi que se nos va que tiene
go to bed tomorrow he has a
que acostarse que mañana tiene un día
great day so nothing kid tomorrow
cojonudo así que nada chaval mañana
more support Frank Cuesta in Kick together we
más apoya a Frank cuesta en Kick juntos
will save the
salvaremos el
sanctuary How good this video This
santuario Qué bueno este vídeo Este
video
vídeo
is keep recording I don't know How bad the
es sigue grabando No s Cómo qué mal lo
past
pasado